technostarry.com 2013-06-05

# Privacy Policy | Technostarry

**Privacy Policy for technostarry.com**

We at technostarry.com take the Privacy Policy of the visitor/user seriously and is extremely important to us. We know that your personal information/details is very important and therefore we ensure that your personal details always remains personal and are never shared with anyone. We do not sell any personal information to any third parties. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.technostarry.com and how it is used.

**Log Files:**  
Like many other Web sites, we make use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.  
**  
Cookies and Web Beacons:**  
We may use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

We also use third party advertisements. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

**What are cookies?**  
A “cookie” is a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters. There are two types of cookies: a persistent cookie and a session cookie. A persistent cookie gets entered by your Web browser into the cookie folder on your computer’s hard drive. A persistent cookie remains in that cookie folder, which is maintained and governed by your Web browser, after you close your browser program. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser.

**DoubleClick DART cookies**  
We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (”interest based targeting”). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting New York, you may see New York hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting [www.google.com/privacy_ads.html ](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partner is Google Adsense.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on technostarry.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as JavaScript, cookies or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

**technostarry.com** have no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. technostarry’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

The work at technostarry.com is licensed under a [Creative Commons 3.0](http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-nd/3.0/). Copying this blog’s content is not allowed.

**Please note:** technostarry.com have a strict no spam policy and do not send you any emails, unless you subscribe to receive email updates.
